So, there it is, people.
Due to budget cutbacks,
we will no longer be offering
free squid guts in the kitchen.
Oh, boo-hoo.
Everyone, look at
my latest invention!
Okay.
I like how it's not
killing us so far.
It takes any object
and makes two smaller copies.
All right!
Why?
You see, as I age,
I've been shrinking
and feeling colder.
So now I need twice as many
sweaters, in a smaller size.
First, I scan
the old sweater.
Then we add some matter.
Any old,
useless matter will do.
Now the matter prism
reorganizes the raw material
into two smaller copies.
So, that's where
baby sweaters come from.
Enclosed as a PDF attachment,
a picture of yourself,
in a boat, on a river.
It's a river that
flows in two directions.
Make that three.
It's a magic river,
that's how.
And it's flowing down
the eerie canal to
The Scary Door.
That's "eerie" with two E's.
Consider,
if you have the energy,
Dr. Daniel Zenus, an inventor
with a terminal case
of"The Lazies."
This robot will do
everything for me.
Robot, activate yourself
and do my research.
Ahh.
Next, assume
my social obligations.
Dr. Zenus,
for a lifetime of
scientific achievement,
we present this award
to your robot.
Daddy, I love you.
Lf only
I'd programmed the robot
to be more careful
what I wished for.
Robot, experience
this tragic irony for me.
No!
Ahh.
Man, I wish we had
a robot to do stuff.
I know, right?
Bender, thank God
I found you in time.
I need someone in the lab
immediately to fold my new sweaters.
I'm sorry, do you see a robot
in this room named "Folder"?
Fortunately, I came prepared
with a back-up phrasing.
Bender, would you mind
bending my new sweaters?
There's only
two of them.
Wait.
You want me to
do two things?
Man, I'd call my lawyer if dialing
a phone wasn't such a hassle.
Razza frazza two things.
Ooh, razza frazza duplicator.
Now for some tasty matter.
Howdy, fellas.
I'm Bender.
Go to hell, old man!
I like your attitude.
Let's party.
But first,
fold these two sweaters.
I'm sorry,
do you see a robot
in this room
named "Folder"?
Damn, you're cute.
Hi. I'm Bender.
This is my robot Bender, and
this is my other robot Bender.
Oh, Lord.
They're 60% scale
replicas of me, Bender.
Does that mean they only
do 60% of the work you do,
or that they actually
do more work
because they're only
60% as lazy?
Shut up.
That's a good one.
Enough good ones, everyone.
We have a delivery to
an alien space giant.
You'll have to
be respectful.
This customer is 50-feet tall and
sensitive about his appearance.
Colossal tooth whitener,
mega deodorant,
humungous acne cream, aww,
and one
regular-sized condom.
All that and a small wiener?
This guy's got it goin' on!
Remember, don't show any
reaction to his appearance.
I hope that's vanishing cream,
'cause that needs to go away.
That's cold-blooded!
Shh!
Lt's okay.
I understand.
My unusual appearance
makes people nervous.
You used humor
to defuse the tension.
Yep, and there's still a little
more tension. So, look out!
You so ugly,
when trick-or-treaters come to
your house, they give you candy.
You so ugly,
when you go to the bank,
they ask you to
put on a ski mask!
You so ugly, you
cracked The Daily Mirror.
It's a newspaper!
I wish it weren't so, but
many of these things are true.
Anyhow, you've lowered
my self-esteem a bit more,
but I'm sincerely grateful
you came all this way
to deliver my fungus chisel.
Don't feel bad, sir.
It's not your fault.
You probably just
inherited your appearance
from your mother.
What?
No one
insults my mama!
God, shield your eyes!
Lt's like Edward
James Olmos on IMAX!
Did you see his face
when I said he so ugly?
No, I blacked out,
'cause he so ugly!
Hey, guys, quit reminiscing
and grab me two cigars.
One thing each?
Sounds fair.
Wait, make that
four cigars.
You want us
to do four things?
My Manwich!
What's up, shorty?
And that's the story
of how one of me became two,
and two became four,
making seven total.
The end.
I just like
having the end locker.
It's not like Amy
cares about it at all.
But no, she won't trade with me.
A rat!
Yes, she is a rat.
No, look!
Which way
to the tiny hookers?
A big, fat roach!
What?
I thought I put that away.
No, there!
Who are you?
Bender sent me.
Hey, I know that guy.
Scruffy, what is that tiny
Bender doing in my soup?
Lt appears to be giving you
the finger, sir. Enjoy.
Help me, help me!
I'm too lazy to escape!
Ow!
What?
This place
is crawling with yous!
So there's more
Benders around.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's good news.
Bad news, everyone.
Look at this
infinite series
representing the mass of
successive generations of Benders.
Don't wait for me.
It's non-convergent!
Oh, dip!
Unless we quickly
exterminate them,
they'll replicate
ad Infinitum
and consume
all the matter on Earth.
According to my calculations, there
are 11 generations at the moment.
That's 2,046 total Benders
we need to destroy.
Wait, does that include me?
Too bad he didn't
have his own Bible.
Just 2,045 more to go.
Creatures have taken
over my house
They want my food
and my skin and my time
Little frogs are okay
but the slugs on the rug
Send me out of my mind
There's no place else
that I can go
The only thing
I can turn to is
Rock 'n'Roll Pest Control
A- wha-ho
A- wha-ho Wha-ho
Rock 'n'Roll Pest Control
A- wha-ho
A- wha-ho Wha-ho
Rock 'n'Roll Pest Control
All right!
Two thousand
forty five, 2,046.
That's it. We got 'em all
except for the big one.
Wait, this isn't
a real Bender.
It's a talking doll from
when Bender had that sitcom
about the city robot
who moves back to the farm.
Shut your pumpkin, bumpkin.
All right, so I let
one measly Bender get away.
How much harm can one infinitely
self-reproducing robot do?
Bender! How could you be
so lazy and irresponsible?
Hey. What? Did someone say I'm great?
What's with the gray goo?
Bite my tiny metal ass!
Hey, those jerklings
ate my couch.
God! We've opened
Pandora's fly.
They'll reproduce
without limit,
consuming all
the matter in the world!
Like the Kardashians.
Now they drank my booze?
They've gone too far!
Wait a second. All Benders
are powered by alcohol!
Of course.
Long before
the Benders devour the Earth,
they'll deplete the
planet's booze and die off.
This is a problem
that will solve itself.
A problem
that solves itself?
That sounds like
a job for me, Bender.
Our top story,
all alcohol on Earth
has mysteriously disappeared.
Consequences are minimal,
except among
the most hardened alcoholics.
Linda?
I can no longer
face my children!
Crisis averted.
Without alcohol, the
Benders are dying off.
A greater tragedy
my eyes have never beheld.
Well, into the toilet.
So sober, so weak.
Things really worked
out nicely this time.
This doesn't taste
like old-man water.
Everyone to
the situation room!
I was lying here snoozing,
dreaming, oddly enough,
about bathing in champagne
with six of the world's
most distinguished scientists,
when suddenly,
I realized my bathwater had
been transformed into alcohol.
Alcohol?
Chug, chug,
chug, chug!
Chug, chug, chug,
Mmm!
Lt's like fine cognac
with a hint of aged scrotum.
How can this be?
I thought the Benders drank
all the alcohol in the world.
They did,
but then they made more!
You see, once the Benders
reached atomic scale,
they began directly manipulating
water and CO2 molecules
to make alcohol.
In a matter of hours,
there will be no more
fresh water on Earth.
No! What will I
mix with my scotch?
Hey, you!
Good evening.
Who are you calling drunk?
You're not drunk. I'm drunk.
That's right, Linda.
Water is now booze,
and everyone's tiddy much
protally fit-shaced.
Turning to sports,
the Indy 500 was today.
There were no survivors.
This chair is so comfortable.
Classic Amy.
You want to see
a picture of my boy?
Sure.
That's your penis.
That's my boy.
I guess this isn't
not so bad.
As long as we don't need
to use our mental...
Mental...
Minds?
What?
No, listen.
I freaking love you.
And I don't throw
that word around.
I know you don't.
That's why I love you.
Are the pizza muffins
ready?
He's here for revenging,
that's why!
No!
Wait! I'm here to apologize.
For your looks?
Nice one.
Well, yes, actually, it
is sort of related to that.
Can we talk?
Grabbing your spaceship was not okay.
I lost my cool,
and I'm sorry.
In group, I learned
that I tend to be a bit...
Repulsive?
Sensitive.
So now I'm, like, trying
to work on my attitude,
and project
an air of positivity.
You're projecting
an alr of something.
Phew!
You're so stinky, you need
Right Guard and left guard.
I'll take your
hygiene advice to heart.
You're ugly!
Hey! Ow!
Yo, freak show!
Your face has been declared
a weapon of mass disgusting.
Timeless.
Okay, deep breath,
deep breath.
Dr. Lesterman?
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I think I'm close
to a temper-control incident.
You have reached the office
of Dr. Judy Lesterman
and Dr. Ira Rothkiss.
The office
is now closed.
If this is
a pharmacy calling...
That's it! I promised myself
I wouldn't do this, but...
I will destroy you all!
I won't stop until your whole planet
is as ugly as you perceive me to be!
That will take
a very long time.
Okay. Stop! Stop!
Stupid...
Blender, you're the
only one who's sober.
You got to do something!
Haven't I done
enough already?
Please, stop the monster.
Just do that one thing!
Make it zero,
and you got a deal.
What if I foldeded the
Professor's sweaters for you?
Both of them?
You mean you'll do two things,
and I only have to do one thing?
Yeah. Just save the world.
Sucker.
Legion of Benders,
come unto me!
We have one thing to do.
Screw that!
Come on,
you lazy jerks!
Lf we all pitch in,
we each only have to do
one quintilllonth of a thing.
All right.
Whoa.
Big Bender starts right now.
Get a shave, ugly!
Oh.
How about some aftershave, dumpy?
You big bully!
You ugly nerd, enjoy a
nice Guggenheim swirly!
Let this beating be a lesson
about never attacking those
more handsome than oneself.
All I wanted was
to apologize to you people.
But now
I have to kill you.
How, by making me look at you?
No. By making you
look at my mama!
Ah!
Your mama's so ugly!
I told you not to
talk about my mama!
Walk toward the light, Bender.
Man, do I have to walk?
No!
Huh?
At last I'm beautiful!
Yeah,
if you're into gray dust.
Bender, you di' it!
No, we di' it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if, together we were able to
defeat this giant space monster,
think how also
we might defeat
the monsters of poverty
and disease and unliteracy.
In this spirit,
I ask my fellow Benders
to join me in
working diligently to...
Boo!
Go to hell!
Come on, let's go someplace
where we don't have to do one
quintillionth of a thing all the time.
Well, that was dumb.
Man, were we drunk.
What happened, Professor?
Something
absolutely incredible!
The sweaters got folded!
But how?
I didn't do it.
Bender, did you learn a
lesson about not being lazy
while the rest of us were
bombed out of our gourds?
Maybe I did, Fry.
Maybe I did.
Or maybe I rescued
one last mini-Bender
to fold stupid, ugly sweaters
while I laughed at him.
I guess we'll never know.